I was waiting for Portland police to come
and they never came.
Then that's what opened my eyes
to what this group is actually doing.
I watched 20 Antifa militants help my assault suspect
escape into an Antifa safe house
that is one block away from the ICE facility.
And this safe house is where Antifa affiliated protestors
are conducting parliamentary operations.
It's where they're arresting, they're showering,
they're eating to continue this occupation.
I have staked out this safe house
and have observed shift changes.
This group is highly organized.
It is being funded through mutual aid groups
and they have no plans of stopping.
Residents living across the ICE facility
have been held hostage by Antifa.
They're begging for federal intervention.
The city refuses to help
and they want you, President Trump,
to come in and restore law and order.
I want to stress the importance
of taking this situation seriously
because when I first started reporting on this occupation,
I went undercover in Blacklock.
I talked to these Antifa militants.
I lasted for about a month.
They believe that ICE agents are the Nazi Gestapo
who need to be killed.
They told me that directly.
And I think that if this situation is not taken
as seriously as it is,
it's just a matter of time before someone gets killed.
And thank you for having me.
Thank you, Katie.
That's pretty incredible.
The only question nobody can answer is why.
Why are they doing this?
They're like insurrectionists.
They're terrible people.
But you really wonder why.
Why are they doing it?
What are they gaining other than they're obviously paid?
They're paid a lot of money.
Go ahead, please.
Mr. President, if I can answer that question,
the reason why they're doing it
is because the same media that's sitting in this room with us
has declared all of us at this table Nazis and fascists.
And they've been doing this for years.
This is why Antifa feels emboldened to attack us.
Now, almost every single person at this table
has been threatened with a steel bat.
We've been assaulted. We've been harassed.
We've been threatened.
And that is in huge part to the media.
So my message right now is for you guys.
Because two years ago, or back in 2020, by the way,
I was censored for my reporting on Antifa
here in Washington, D.C.
You were talking about how safe it is.
Now, Mr. President, it wasn't so safe back then.
Back in 2020, I watched as a father
was being mobbed and surrounded by Antifa members
as his terrified, crying children looked on
and the police here did nothing.
I watched as a woman had her hair violently
ripped out of her skull simply for waving an American flag
on the streets of Washington, D.C.
And by the way, if you guys try to go and find
any of this footage, you won't find any of it
because Twitter deleted all of it
because our president shared my reporting
and they deleted my entire account immediately after.
So now, if you want to know what happened in 2020,
all you're going to see is the media headlines that said
it was fiery but mostly peaceful.
Thanks for that one, CNN.
The reality is that it was an extremely violent period
of time, and for the last 10 years,
Antifa has been wrecking havoc on law-abiding
and innocent American citizens, and it needs to end.
Now, I'm with Turning Point USA.
It's an honor to be here, Mr. President.
Thank you guys so much, everybody in the administration,
for giving us a seat at the table
because the media has not only been demonizing us for so long,
but immediately after the brutal assassination
of our founder, Charlie Kirk,
our Turning Point USA chapters have seen an uptick
in violence across the nation as Antifa chapters
that are embedded in our universities go and target them.